{"data":[{"question":"Is this the address to ________ you want the package sent?","a":"where","b":"that","c":"which","d":"whom","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To which = where.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"That book is by a famous anthropologist. It's about the people in Samoa ________ for two years.","a":"that she lived","b":"that she lived among them","c":"among whom she lived","d":"where she lived among them","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Whom: object pronoun for people \u00a0\n- If a preposition is used with the relative pronoun, this preposition can either precede the pronoun or follow the verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time Jason arrived to help, we ________ moving everything.","a":"has already finished","b":"had already finished","c":"already finished","d":"already finish","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (By the time Jason arrived to help).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The apartment was hot when I got home, so I ________ the air conditioner.","a":"had turned on","b":"turn on","c":"turned on","d":"would turn on","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tense agreement: When the main clause is in past tense, in the subordinate clause the past tense shows another completed action related in time to the main action.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"We engaged a ________ to show us the way across the mountains.","a":"guidance","b":"guide","c":"guided","d":"guideless","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A + Noun.\u00a0\n- Guide: someone whose job is to take tourists to a place and show them around.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The farmer's barn caught fire during the night. By the time the fire fighters arrived, the building ________ to the ground.","a":"burned","b":"had been burned","c":"was burned","d":"had burned","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (By the time the fire fighters arrived).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The suit cost me more than a week's salary. Until then, I ________ so much on one outfit.","a":"never had spent","b":"never has spent","c":"had never spent","d":"has never spent","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (Until then).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Yesterday a hornet ________ me under my arm. That really hurt! When I put on my shirt after working in the garden, I hadn't seen that there was a hornet in it.","a":"had stung","b":"sting","c":"stung","d":"was stung","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (yesterday).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Sophie is very keen ________ to art college.","a":"in going","b":"at going","c":"about going","d":"on going","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be keen sth\/doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"If any of your questions are still ________, you could do some more research in order to have answers.","a":"inanswered","b":"unanswered","c":"imanswered","d":"iranswered","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Unanswered (adj) an unanswered question has not been answered.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}